<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSIS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="mission_statement">
        The mission of the Department of Computer Science and Information
        at SVSU is to provide an outstanding education to its students in
        accordance with the guidelines of the SVSU mission, to advance scholarship
        in the key domains of the computing and information systems sciences, and
        to engage in activities that improve the welfare of society and enhance the reputation of SVSU.</string>
    <string name="the_rest_of_it">

        The department will provide its students with balanced programs which emphasize:

        the knowledge of the core principles of computer science
        the skills necessary to use computers to solve real-world problems
        experience in implementing solutions with modern computing tools
        the communication skills necessary to work effectively in a team
        foster a high level of faculty/student interaction and mentoring
        At the end of their programs at SVSU, the department expects CSIS students to be able to:

        Solve problems by using skills in math, computer science, and technology
        Design, implement, document and maintain computer systems
        Communicate effectively both orally and in writing
        Understand professional, ethical, legal, security and social issues and responsibilities
        Apply their knowledge and skills as they start their professional careers
        Work well both independently and collaboratively with diverse groups
        Generate new and creative ideas

        After the successful completion of their degree requirements at SVSU:

        Graduates shall demonstrate a thorough grounding in the fundamental principles and practices
        of computing and information systems, and those principles that underpin them.
        Graduates shall demonstrate an understanding of the contexts in which computing is applied.
        Graduates shall find employment in the computing profession and/or continue advanced studies
        in computer science or information systems. </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
